Sandhya Lalasaheb Mane

SUMMARY

Over 12 years of experience in multiple technologies including Desktop, Web, Mobile application development. Was currently working in automations as a senior DevOps engineer with around 4 years of experience. Versatility in quickly adapting to new coding conventions is combined with a 'can-do' attitude. This means I am happy working independently or in a close team environment, and apply a positive attitude to every project.

KEY SKILLS

Toc	hnologies:	_			т	Tools:-	
IEC	illologies.	-	Kubernetes, Terraform			10013	
	Core J	ava	>	Fission	>	Nexus	
	.Net		>	Redis	>	Git Repository	
	Angula	ar JS	>	Elasticsearch	>	Jenkins	
S	Pytho	n	>	AWS			
	Docke	r					

CERTIFICATES

AWS Solution Architect- Associate - Aug 2023

WORK EXPERIENCE

Accenture Solutions Private Limited (May 2021 – Present)

Description: Got a chance to work on below projects. From 17th July 2022 to 13th Feb 2023 I was on Maternity leave.

➤ <u>Daily Close (DB client)</u>: Part of SAP DevOps team, achieved Continuous integration with Continuous testing for SAP system. CI has been achieved using TeamCity and Continuous testing with report generation through Tosca. Also done POC for automatic Defect creation ALM tool.

Roles and Responsibilities: Design and implement the DevOps pipeline

System Specifications:-

- Technologies: TeamCity, Jira, ALM integration, Tosca integration, Groovy scripting, SOLMAN integration
- MS Platform (UBS client): This project itself includes multiple tools. I was part of DevOps team for handling CICD pipelines and respective work for all these tools.

Roles and Responsibilities: Managing DevOps pipeline

System Specifications:-

Technologies: Jenkins

Amdocs India Pvt. Ltd(July 2016 - Apr 2021)

Description: Got a chance to work on below projects

> <u>SRE Automation Platform</u>: Platform developed to implement Google's concept of SRE [Site Reliability Engineering]. This platform has been developed and implemented to handle Operation Teams work effectively by automating redundant tasks and making them available to all other customers for reuse. I would say, this is one of the best Project.

Roles and Responsibilities: Development with leading Implementation on Customer network

System Specifications:-

- Technologies: Python, kubernetes, docker, fission (serverless functions), nifi, kafka, zookeeper, orchestrator, AWS integration, Jenkins, Gitlab, Nexus
- ➤ <u>Business KPI Dashboard</u>: Hybrid Mobile application for higher management who are interested in Business KPI's at any point of time and expecting updated correct data on all platforms. Using this App, all main business KPI's has been captured. To make it available on Web + Mobile [cross-platform] with same code base, it is developed as Hybrid App using Ionic. I was leading this application, and was implemented in 8-10 accounts.

Roles and Responsibilities: – Implementation and leading it with client **System Specifications:**-

• Technologies: Ionic, Oracle, Advanced Java

Yash Technologies Pvt. Ltd(As a Contingent in John Deere India Pvt. Ltd) (July 2010 – Dec 2015)

Description: On payroll of Yash Technology Pvt. Ltd. ltd client side John Deere Indis Pvt Ltd.

Got chance to work on multiple projects

> **OLFM Mobility System**: [Oracle lease and finance management] Android Mobile application for loan assessment of John Deere products. Handing loan eligibility check by capturing required data with documents, EMI Calculations and collection, receipt printing using Bluetooth printer.

Roles and Responsibilities: Worked on all phases from Planning to support.

System Specifications:-

Technologies: Android 4.4, Core Java, Rest and Soap Web services

Database: SQLite

> **Drip Irrigation System**: Android Mobile Application for handling Drip Irrigation plantation. Purpose was to irrigate whole land in available water by calculating required water pressure. The calculations were depending on number of pips, valves, plants etc.

Roles and Responsibilities: Planning, Analysis, Designing, Development, Unit Testing

System Specifications:-

Technologies: Android 4.4, Core Java

Database: SQLite

ALiss: ALiss stands for Assembly Line Solution Set. Desktop application to help tractor manufacturing process to create an optimal plan by reducing all the wastes of manufacturing process like idle time, overproduction, defective Products, Over Processing, Unnecessary row material, time wasted in transportation and motion.

Roles and Responsibilities: Planning, Analysis, Designing, Development, Unit Testing

System Specifications:-

Technologies: WPF

• Database: Microsoft Access as database

Avanti Software Solutions Pvt Ltd (Jan 2010 – July 2010)

Description: Small scale company who gave me experience on all the phase of software development. I have worked there for around 6 months, during that period I have worked on below projects.

- > Citizen Facilitation Center Of Government: Desktop application to enable users with government facilities like birth and death registration, certificates, taxes related help, complaints and so on.
- Nagarpalika Automation System: Desktop application to automate the manual work of Nagarpalika office. Focus was on Report generation.
- College Automation System: Desktop application to automate the manual work of college office. Here too the Focus was on report generation.

Roles and Responsibilities: Design, Development, testing, support System Specifications:-

Technologies: C#.netDatabase: SQL Server 2005

EDUCATION

- Master In computer Application. (First Class: 2009)s
- Bachelor in Science (Math) (First Class: 2006)
- 12th From Kolhapur University. (Pass class: 2003)
- SSC from Kolhapur Board. (Pass class: 2001)